'use strict';var quizObj={0:{title:'Simple Present – Exercise 1',0:{question:'I usually <span><input class="inline-input" type="text" id="quiz-0-0" style="display: inline; width: 30%; padding: 3px 8px; font-size: 13px; border-radius: 3px; border: 1px solid #ccc;"></span> (go) to school.',answer:'go'},1:{question:'They <span><input class="inline-input" type="text" id="quiz-0-1" style="display: inline; width: 30%; padding: 3px 8px; font-size: 13px; border-radius: 3px; border: 1px solid #ccc;"></span> (visit) us often.',answer:'visit'},2:{question:'You <span><input class="inline-input" type="text" id="quiz-0-2" style="display: inline; width: 30%; padding: 3px 8px; font-size: 13px; border-radius: 3px; border: 1px solid #ccc;"></span> (play) basketball once a week.',answer:'play'},3:{question:'Tom <span><input class="inline-input" type="text" id="quiz-0-3" style="display: inline; width: 30%; padding: 3px 8px; font-size: 13px; border-radius: 3px; border: 1px solid #ccc;"></span> (work) every day.',answer:'works'},4:{question:'He always <span><input class="inline-input" type="text" id="quiz-0-4" style="display: inline; width: 30%; padding: 3px 8px; font-size: 13px; border-radius: 3px; border: 1px solid #ccc;"></span> (tell) us funny stories.',answer:'tells'},5:{question:'She never <span><input class="inline-input" type="text" id="quiz-0-5" style="display: inline; width: 30%; padding: 3px 8px; font-size: 13px; border-radius: 3px; border: 1px solid #ccc;"></span> (help) me with that!',answer:'helps'},6:{question:'Martha and Kevin <span><input class="inline-input" type="text" id="quiz-0-6" style="display: inline; width: 30%; padding: 3px 8px; font-size: 13px; border-radius: 3px; border: 1px solid #ccc;"></span> (swim) twice a week.',answer:'swim'},7:{question:'In this club people usually <span><input class="inline-input" type="text" id="quiz-0-7" style="display: inline; width: 30%; padding: 3px 8px; font-size: 13px; border-radius: 3px; border: 1px solid #ccc;"></span> (dance) a lot.',answer:'dance'},8:{question:'Linda <span><input class="inline-input" type="text" id="quiz-0-8" style="display: inline; width: 30%; padding: 3px 8px; font-size: 13px; border-radius: 3px; border: 1px solid #ccc;"></span> (take care) of her sister.',answer:'takes care'},9:{question:'John rarely <span><input class="inline-input" type="text" id="quiz-0-9" style="display: inline; width: 30%; padding: 3px 8px; font-size: 13px; border-radius: 3px; border: 1px solid #ccc;"></span> (leave) the country.',answer:'leaves'},10:{question:'We <span><input class="inline-input" type="text" id="quiz-0-10" style="display: inline; width: 30%; padding: 3px 8px; font-size: 13px; border-radius: 3px; border: 1px solid #ccc;"></span> (live) in the city most of the year.',answer:'live'},11:{question:'Lorie <span><input class="inline-input" type="text" id="quiz-0-11" style="display: inline; width: 30%; padding: 3px 8px; font-size: 13px; border-radius: 3px; border: 1px solid #ccc;"></span> (travel) to Paris every Sunday.',answer:'travels'},12:{question:'I <span><input class="inline-input" type="text" id="quiz-0-12" style="display: inline; width: 30%; padding: 3px 8px; font-size: 13px; border-radius: 3px; border: 1px solid #ccc;"></span> (bake) cookies twice a month.',answer:'bake'},13:{question:'You always <span><input class="inline-input" type="text" id="quiz-0-13" style="display: inline; width: 30%; padding: 3px 8px; font-size: 13px; border-radius: 3px; border: 1px solid #ccc;"></span> (teach) me new things.',answer:'teach'},14:{question:'She <span><input class="inline-input" type="text" id="quiz-0-14" style="display: inline; width: 30%; padding: 3px 8px; font-size: 13px; border-radius: 3px; border: 1px solid #ccc;"></span> (help) the kids of the neighborhood.',answer:'helps'}},1:{title:'Simple Present – Exercise 2',0:{question:'London <span><input class="inline-input" type="text" id="quiz-1-0" style="display: inline; width: 30%; padding: 3px 8px; font-size: 13px; border-radius: 3px; border: 1px solid #ccc;"></span> (be) in England',answer:'is'},1:{question:'The summer <span><input class="inline-input" type="text" id="quiz-1-1" style="display: inline; width: 30%; padding: 3px 8px; font-size: 13px; border-radius: 3px; border: 1px solid #ccc;"></span> (be) hot.',answer:'is'},2:{question:'She <span><input class="inline-input" type="text" id="quiz-1-2" style="display: inline; width: 30%; padding: 3px 8px; font-size: 13px; border-radius: 3px; border: 1px solid #ccc;"></span> (drive) very well.',answer:'drives'},3:{question:'They <span><input class="inline-input" type="text" id="quiz-1-3" style="display: inline; width: 30%; padding: 3px 8px; font-size: 13px; border-radius: 3px; border: 1px solid #ccc;"></span> (open) the store at 8:00.',answer:'open'},4:{question:'Linda <span><input class="inline-input" type="text" id="quiz-1-4" style="display: inline; width: 30%; padding: 3px 8px; font-size: 13px; border-radius: 3px; border: 1px solid #ccc;"></span> (be) a very pretty girl.',answer:'is'},5:{question:'I <span><input class="inline-input" type="text" id="quiz-1-5" style="display: inline; width: 30%; padding: 3px 8px; font-size: 13px; border-radius: 3px; border: 1px solid #ccc;"></span> (have) several jobs.',answer:'have'},6:{question:'Water <span><input class="inline-input" type="text" id="quiz-1-6" style="display: inline; width: 30%; padding: 3px 8px; font-size: 13px; border-radius: 3px; border: 1px solid #ccc;"></span> (boil) at 100 degrees.',answer:'boils'},7:{question:'Water <span><input class="inline-input" type="text" id="quiz-1-7" style="display: inline; width: 30%; padding: 3px 8px; font-size: 13px; border-radius: 3px; border: 1px solid #ccc;"></span> (freeze) at 0 degrees.',answer:'freezes'},8:{question:'My sister  <span><input class="inline-input" type="text" id="quiz-1-8" style="display: inline; width: 30%; padding: 3px 8px; font-size: 13px; border-radius: 3px; border: 1px solid #ccc;"></span> (speak) English.',answer:'speaks'},9:{question:'He <span><input class="inline-input" type="text" id="quiz-1-9" style="display: inline; width: 30%; padding: 3px 8px; font-size: 13px; border-radius: 3px; border: 1px solid #ccc;"></span> (have) a big apartment.',answer:'has'},10:{question:'A triangle <span><input class="inline-input" type="text" id="quiz-1-10" style="display: inline; width: 30%; padding: 3px 8px; font-size: 13px; border-radius: 3px; border: 1px solid #ccc;"></span> (have) three corners.',answer:'has'},11:{question:'My birthday <span><input class="inline-input" type="text" id="quiz-1-11" style="display: inline; width: 30%; padding: 3px 8px; font-size: 13px; border-radius: 3px; border: 1px solid #ccc;"></span> (be) in June.',answer:'is'},12:{question:'Books <span><input class="inline-input" type="text" id="quiz-1-12" style="display: inline; width: 30%; padding: 3px 8px; font-size: 13px; border-radius: 3px; border: 1px solid #ccc;"></span> (have) pages.',answer:'have'},13:{question:'Dogs <span><input class="inline-input" type="text" id="quiz-1-13" style="display: inline; width: 30%; padding: 3px 8px; font-size: 13px; border-radius: 3px; border: 1px solid #ccc;"></span> (be) good friends.',answer:'are'},14:{question:'I <span><input class="inline-input" type="text" id="quiz-1-14" style="display: inline; width: 30%; padding: 3px 8px; font-size: 13px; border-radius: 3px; border: 1px solid #ccc;"></span> (work) hard.',answer:'work'}},2:{title:'Simple Present – Exercise 3',0:{question:'I <span><input class="inline-input" type="text" id="quiz-2-0" style="display: inline; width: 30%; padding: 3px 8px; font-size: 13px; border-radius: 3px; border: 1px solid #ccc;"></span> (love) you.',answer:'love'},1:{question:'This <span><input class="inline-input" type="text" id="quiz-2-1" style="display: inline; width: 30%; padding: 3px 8px; font-size: 13px; border-radius: 3px; border: 1px solid #ccc;"></span> (weigh) 20 kilograms.',answer:'weighs'},2:{question:'Ron <span><input class="inline-input" type="text" id="quiz-2-2" style="display: inline; width: 30%; padding: 3px 8px; font-size: 13px; border-radius: 3px; border: 1px solid #ccc;"></span> (seem) serious.',answer:'seems'},3:{question:'We <span><input class="inline-input" type="text" id="quiz-2-3" style="display: inline; width: 30%; padding: 3px 8px; font-size: 13px; border-radius: 3px; border: 1px solid #ccc;"></span> (like) tomatoes.',answer:'like'},4:{question:'The boy <span><input class="inline-input" type="text" id="quiz-2-4" style="display: inline; width: 30%; padding: 3px 8px; font-size: 13px; border-radius: 3px; border: 1px solid #ccc;"></span> (want) to play.',answer:'wants'},5:{question:'You <span><input class="inline-input" type="text" id="quiz-2-5" style="display: inline; width: 30%; padding: 3px 8px; font-size: 13px; border-radius: 3px; border: 1px solid #ccc;"></span> (need) to sleep.',answer:'need'},6:{question:'They <span><input class="inline-input" type="text" id="quiz-2-6" style="display: inline; width: 30%; padding: 3px 8px; font-size: 13px; border-radius: 3px; border: 1px solid #ccc;"></span> (agree) with me.',answer:'agree'},7:{question:'She <span><input class="inline-input" type="text" id="quiz-2-7" style="display: inline; width: 30%; padding: 3px 8px; font-size: 13px; border-radius: 3px; border: 1px solid #ccc;"></span> (hear) something strange.',answer:'hears'},8:{question:'The box <span><input class="inline-input" type="text" id="quiz-2-8" style="display: inline; width: 30%; padding: 3px 8px; font-size: 13px; border-radius: 3px; border: 1px solid #ccc;"></span> (contain) food.',answer:'contains'},9:{question:'Emma <span><input class="inline-input" type="text" id="quiz-2-9" style="display: inline; width: 30%; padding: 3px 8px; font-size: 13px; border-radius: 3px; border: 1px solid #ccc;"></span> (appear) sad.',answer:'appears'},10:{question:'David <span><input class="inline-input" type="text" id="quiz-2-10" style="display: inline; width: 30%; padding: 3px 8px; font-size: 13px; border-radius: 3px; border: 1px solid #ccc;"></span> (know) how to fix a car.',answer:'knows'},11:{question:'Daniel and Liz <span><input class="inline-input" type="text" id="quiz-2-11" style="display: inline; width: 30%; padding: 3px 8px; font-size: 13px; border-radius: 3px; border: 1px solid #ccc;"></span> (seem) happy.',answer:'seem'},12:{question:'This <span><input class="inline-input" type="text" id="quiz-2-12" style="display: inline; width: 30%; padding: 3px 8px; font-size: 13px; border-radius: 3px; border: 1px solid #ccc;"></span> (smell) bad.',answer:'smells'},13:{question:'I <span><input class="inline-input" type="text" id="quiz-2-13" style="display: inline; width: 30%; padding: 3px 8px; font-size: 13px; border-radius: 3px; border: 1px solid #ccc;"></span> (believe) you.',answer:'believe'},14:{question:'We <span><input class="inline-input" type="text" id="quiz-2-14" style="display: inline; width: 30%; padding: 3px 8px; font-size: 13px; border-radius: 3px; border: 1px solid #ccc;"></span> (be) number one!',answer:'are'}},3:{title:'Present Progressive – Exercise 1',0:{question:'Anna <span><input class="inline-input" type="text" id="quiz-3-0" style="display: inline; width: 30%; padding: 3px 8px; font-size: 13px; border-radius: 3px; border: 1px solid #ccc;"></span> (rest) right now.',answer:'is resting'},1:{question:'I <span><input class="inline-input" type="text" id="quiz-3-1" style="display: inline; width: 30%; padding: 3px 8px; font-size: 13px; border-radius: 3px; border: 1px solid #ccc;"></span> (talk) on the phone at this moment.',answer:'am talking'},2:{question:'Bella <span><input class="inline-input" type="text" id="quiz-3-2" style="display: inline; width: 30%; padding: 3px 8px; font-size: 13px; border-radius: 3px; border: 1px solid #ccc;"></span> (cook) dinner now.',answer:'is cooking'},3:{question:'They <span><input class="inline-input" type="text" id="quiz-3-3" style="display: inline; width: 30%; padding: 3px 8px; font-size: 13px; border-radius: 3px; border: 1px solid #ccc;"></span> (help) the teacher right now.',answer:'are helping'},4:{question:'He <span><input class="inline-input" type="text" id="quiz-3-4" style="display: inline; width: 30%; padding: 3px 8px; font-size: 13px; border-radius: 3px; border: 1px solid #ccc;"></span> (run) very fast!',answer:'is running'},5:{question:'Julia <span><input class="inline-input" type="text" id="quiz-3-5" style="display: inline; width: 30%; padding: 3px 8px; font-size: 13px; border-radius: 3px; border: 1px solid #ccc;"></span> (bake) a chocolate cake at the moment.',answer:'is baking'},6:{question:'I <span><input class="inline-input" type="text" id="quiz-3-6" style="display: inline; width: 30%; padding: 3px 8px; font-size: 13px; border-radius: 3px; border: 1px solid #ccc;"></span> (have) fun!',answer:'am having'},7:{question:'You <span><input class="inline-input" type="text" id="quiz-3-7" style="display: inline; width: 30%; padding: 3px 8px; font-size: 13px; border-radius: 3px; border: 1px solid #ccc;"></span> (dance) very nicely.',answer:'are dancing'},8:{question:'They <span><input class="inline-input" type="text" id="quiz-3-8" style="display: inline; width: 30%; padding: 3px 8px; font-size: 13px; border-radius: 3px; border: 1px solid #ccc;"></span> (answer) all the questions.',answer:'are answering'},9:{question:'John <span><input class="inline-input" type="text" id="quiz-3-9" style="display: inline; width: 30%; padding: 3px 8px; font-size: 13px; border-radius: 3px; border: 1px solid #ccc;"></span> (eat) Salad, and I am eating fish.',answer:'is eating'},10:{question:'Marta <span><input class="inline-input" type="text" id="quiz-3-10" style="display: inline; width: 30%; padding: 3px 8px; font-size: 13px; border-radius: 3px; border: 1px solid #ccc;"></span> (drive), and Chris is sleeping (sleep).',answer:'is driving'},11:{question:'It <span><input class="inline-input" type="text" id="quiz-3-11" style="display: inline; width: 30%; padding: 3px 8px; font-size: 13px; border-radius: 3px; border: 1px solid #ccc;"></span> (rain).',answer:'is raining'},12:{question:'I <span><input class="inline-input" type="text" id="quiz-3-12" style="display: inline; width: 30%; padding: 3px 8px; font-size: 13px; border-radius: 3px; border: 1px solid #ccc;"></span> (write) my homework.',answer:'am writing'},13:{question:'We <span><input class="inline-input" type="text" id="quiz-3-13" style="display: inline; width: 30%; padding: 3px 8px; font-size: 13px; border-radius: 3px; border: 1px solid #ccc;"></span> (work) on the new show right now.',answer:'are working'},14:{question:'Kate <span><input class="inline-input" type="text" id="quiz-3-14" style="display: inline; width: 30%; padding: 3px 8px; font-size: 13px; border-radius: 3px; border: 1px solid #ccc;"></span> (lie) in bed now.',answer:'is lying'}}};function displayQuiz(range){var key,li,successNode;var quizzes=document.getElementById('quizzes_'+range);quizzes.innerHTML="";for(key in quizObj[range]){if(!quizObj[range].hasOwnProperty(key)){continue;}
if(key!=='title'){successNode=document.createElement('SPAN');successNode.style.cssText='font-weight: bold; font-size: 25px; margin-left: 5px; vertical-align: middle;';li=document.createElement("LI");li.style.cssText='margin-bottom: 5px; height: 28px';li.innerHTML=Number(key)+1+'. '+quizObj[range][key].question;li.appendChild(successNode);quizzes.appendChild(li);}
else{document.getElementById('quiz_tile_'+range).innerText=quizObj[range][key];}}}
var buttonMouseOver=function(){this.style.backgroundColor='#449d44';this.style.borderColor='#398439';};var buttonMouseOut=function(){this.style.backgroundColor='#5cb85c';this.style.borderColor='#4cae4c';};var buttonClick=function(){var percent=0,type='',message='';var i,inputId,quizKey,answer;var parentSpan,alertNode,strongNode,spanNode,spanForMessage;var range=this.getAttribute('id').replace('check_quiz_','');var quizzes=document.getElementById('quizzes_'+range);var inputs=quizzes.getElementsByClassName('inline-input');for(i=0;i<inputs.length;i+=1){parentSpan=inputs[i].parentElement;inputId=inputs[i].getAttribute('id');answer=inputs[i].value;quizKey=inputId.replace('quiz-'+range+'-','');if(quizObj[range][quizKey].answer===answer){percent+=6.66;if(inputs[i].style.display!=='none'){spanNode=document.createElement('SPAN');spanNode.style.cssText='font-weight: bold; font-style: italic';spanNode.innerText=answer;parentSpan.appendChild(spanNode);parentSpan.parentElement.lastChild.style.color='#449d44';parentSpan.parentElement.lastChild.innerHTML='&check;';inputs[i].style.display='none';}}
else{parentSpan.parentElement.lastChild.style.color='red';parentSpan.parentElement.lastChild.innerHTML='&times;';}}
percent=Math.ceil(percent);alertNode=document.createElement('DIV');alertNode.style.cssText='text-align: center; padding: 10px; margin-bottom: 20px; border: 1px solid transparent; border-radius: 4px;';if(percent===0){alertNode.style.color='#a94442';alertNode.style.backgroundColor='#f2dede';alertNode.style.borderColor='#ebccd1';type='Goose Egg! ';message='Your score is '+percent+'%.';}
else if(percent>0&&percent<=20){alertNode.style.color='#a94442';alertNode.style.backgroundColor='#f2dede';alertNode.style.borderColor='#ebccd1';type='Try Again! ';message='Your score is '+percent+'%.';}
else if(percent>20&&percent<=40){alertNode.style.color='#a94442';alertNode.style.backgroundColor='#f2dede';alertNode.style.borderColor='#ebccd1';type='You Need More Practice! ';message='Your score is '+percent+'%.';}
else if(percent>40&&percent<60){alertNode.style.color='#8a6d3b';alertNode.style.backgroundColor='#fcf8e3';alertNode.style.borderColor='#faebcc';type='Middle of the Road! ';message='Your score is '+percent+'%.';}
else if(percent>60&&percent<=80){alertNode.style.color='#8a6d3b';alertNode.style.backgroundColor='#fcf8e3';alertNode.style.borderColor='#faebcc';type='Good Job! ';message='Your score is '+percent+'%.';}
else if(percent>80&&percent<100){alertNode.style.color='#31708f';alertNode.style.backgroundColor='#d9edf7';alertNode.style.borderColor='#bce8f1';type='Great Job! ';message='Your score is '+percent+'%.';}
else if(percent===100){alertNode.style.color='#3c763d';alertNode.style.backgroundColor='#dff0d8';alertNode.style.borderColor='#d6e9c6';type='Perfect! ';message='Your score is '+percent+'%.';}
strongNode=document.createElement('STRONG');strongNode.innerText=type;spanForMessage=document.createElement('SPAN');spanForMessage.innerHTML=message;alertNode.appendChild(strongNode);alertNode.appendChild(spanForMessage);var messageForScoreNode=document.getElementById('message_for_score_'+range);messageForScoreNode.innerHTML='';messageForScoreNode.appendChild(alertNode);};var executeCode=function(){var quizEmbedContainers=document.getElementsByClassName('quiz_embed_container');var j;var range,quizTitleNode,quizDesc,messageForScoreNode,quizzes,buttonContainerNode,checkButtonNode;for(j=0;j<quizEmbedContainers.length;j+=1){range=quizEmbedContainers[j].getAttribute("range-of-quiz");quizEmbedContainers[j].style.cssText='background-color: #f5f5f5; border: 1px solid #e3e3e3; border-radius: 4px; padding: 19px; margin-bottom: 20px;';quizTitleNode=document.createElement("P");quizTitleNode.style.cssText='text-align: center; font-weight: bold; font-size: 18px; margin: 10px 0;';quizTitleNode.setAttribute('id','quiz_tile_'+range);quizDesc=document.createElement('P');quizDesc.style.cssText='text-align: center; margin-bottom: 20px; font-weight: bold;';messageForScoreNode=document.createElement("DIV");messageForScoreNode.setAttribute('id','message_for_score_'+range);quizzes=document.createElement('UL');quizzes.style.cssText='list-style-type: none; padding: 0 20px; margin-top: 0; margin-bottom: 10px;';quizzes.setAttribute('id','quizzes_'+range);buttonContainerNode=document.createElement("DIV");buttonContainerNode.style.cssText='text-align: center; margin-bottom: 20px;';checkButtonNode=document.createElement("BUTTON");checkButtonNode.style.cssText='padding: 4px 6px; color: #fff; background-color: #5cb85c; border-color: #4cae4c; border-radius: 4px; border: 1px solid transparent;';checkButtonNode.setAttribute('id','check_quiz_'+range);checkButtonNode.setAttribute('class','check_quiz');checkButtonNode.innerText='Check';quizEmbedContainers[j].appendChild(quizTitleNode);quizEmbedContainers[j].appendChild(messageForScoreNode);quizEmbedContainers[j].appendChild(quizDesc);quizEmbedContainers[j].appendChild(quizzes);quizEmbedContainers[j].appendChild(buttonContainerNode);buttonContainerNode.appendChild(checkButtonNode);displayQuiz(range);}
var checkButtons=document.getElementsByClassName('check_quiz');var k;for(k=0;k<checkButtons.length;k+=1){checkButtons[k].addEventListener('mouseover',buttonMouseOver,false);checkButtons[k].addEventListener('mouseout',buttonMouseOut,false);checkButtons[k].addEventListener('click',buttonClick,false);}};executeCode();